hancinema.net 2018-12-28

# HanCinema Privacy Policy Statement @ HanCinema :: The Korean Movie and Drama Database

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages Visitors access or visit, user-specific information on what pages Visitors access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify Visitors about updates to our Web site, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact Visitors for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by visiting us by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

[DoubleClick](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx) (To "opt-out"), [Tribal Fusion](http://exponential.com/privacy/), [Google](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) and [Google ads privacy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [Webgains](http://www.webgains.com/privacy.html), [YesAsia](http://global.yesasia.com/help/Section.aspx?sectionId=651&lang=en), [YesStyle](http://www.yesstyle.com/en/Help/Section.aspx?section=cs&sectionId=754), [DramaFever](http://www.dramafever.com/privacypolicy.html/), [PubGalaxy](https://www.pubgalaxy.com/), [Quantcast](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/), [Chartbeat](https://chartbeat.com/privacy/), [Alexa](https://www.alexa.com/help/privacy), [Disqus](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy)

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Regarding Expronential :   
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) policy or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Visitors may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them.

Visitors can access this information by e-mail us at the above address by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message.

Visitors can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message or by phone.

Our postal address is   
**5392 208 St  
Langley, BC V3A 2J9 - Canada**

We can be reached via e-mail by clicking here, Contact, and leaving us a message.  
or you can reach us by telephone at 604 725 2413
